let quiz = [
    {
        question: "Lord Rama was belonging to which generation?",
        option: [
            "Surya Vansh",
            "Yadu Vansh",
            "Chandra Vansh",
            "Raghu Vansh",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "Who was Lord Rama's Guru?",
        option: [
            "Guru Shukracharya",
            "Guru Vishwamitra",
            "Guru Vaishitha ",
            "Guru Dronacharya",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
         question: "Who was the mother of Goddess Sita?",
        option: [
            "Tara",
            "Sunayana",
            "Simhika",
            "Sulochana",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question:
            "What was the name of Lord Shiva's Bow which was broken by Lord Rama?",
        option: [
            "Gandeev",
            "Koumodaki",
            "Vijaya",
            "Pinaka",
        ],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question:
            "Who was Jatayu's brother?",
        option: [
            "Aruna",
            "Mareecha",
            "Sampathi",
            "Jambavanta",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "What was the name of Sugreeva's Wife?",
        option: [
            "Tara", 
            "Roma", 
            "Mandodari", 
            "Jahnavi"],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "Who was the son of Hanumana?",
        option: [
            "Sasdhwaja",
            "Kumarveera",
            "Makardhwaja",
            "Sasula",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question:
            "What was the name of Ravana's mother?",
        option: [
            "Mandodari", 
            "Kaikesi", 
            "Trishera", 
            "Kumbhini"],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "Choose the correct relation between Hidimba-Ravana?",
        option: [
            "Sister-in-law  - Father",
             "Sister-Brother", 
             "Cousins", 
             "No-relation"],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "How many days did Lord Rama and Ravana fight a fierce battle?",
        option: [
            "15", 
            "30", 
            "7", 
            "45"],
        answer: 3,
    },
];
